<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<search>
    <entry index="6">
        <url><![CDATA[孔子2.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 孔子2.html]]></title>
        <content><![CDATA[三人行，必有我师焉。择其善者而从之，其不善者而改之。 When I walk along with two others, they may serve me as my teachers. I will select their good qualities and follow them,their bad qualities and avoid them. 己所不欲，勿施于人。 What you do not want done to yourself, do not do to others. 有朋自远方来，不亦乐乎？ Is it not delightful to have friends coming from distant quarters? ]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry index="7">
        <url><![CDATA[孔子3.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 孔子3.html]]></title>
        <content><![CDATA[人不知而不愠，不亦君子乎？ Is he not a man of complete virtue, who feels no discomposure though men may take no note of him? 道不同，不相为谋。 Those whose courses are different can not lay plans for one another. 唯女子与小人，为难养也。近之则不孙，远之则怨。 Of all people, girls and servants are the most difficult to behave to. If you are familiar with them, they lose their humility. If you maintain a reserve towards them, they are discontented. ]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry index="8">
        <url><![CDATA[孔子4.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 孔子4.html]]></title>
        <content><![CDATA[吾十有五而志于学，三十而立，四十而不惑，五十而知天命，六十而耳顺，七十而从心所欲，不逾矩。 At fifteen I set my heart upon learning. At thirty, I planted my feet firm upon the ground. At forty, I no longer suffered from perplexities. At fifty, I knew what were the biddings of Heaven. At sixty,I heard them with docile ear. At seventy, I could follow the dictates of my own heart; for what I desired no longer overstepped the boundaries of right. 不患人之不己知，患不知人也。 I will not be afflicted at men’s not knowing me; I will be afflicted that I do not know men. ]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry index="9">
        <url><![CDATA[孔子5.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 孔子5.html]]></title>
        <content><![CDATA[工欲善其事，必先利其器。 A craftsman who wishes to do his work well must first sharpen his tools. 君子欲讷于言，而敏于行。 The superior man wishes to be slow in his speech and earnest in his conduct. 君子成人之美，不成人之恶，小人反是。 The superior man seeks to perfect the admirable qualities of men, and does not seek to perfect their bad qualities.The mean man does the opposite of this. 性相近也，习相远也。 By nature, men are nearly alike; by practice, they get to be wide apart. ]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry index="10">
        <url><![CDATA[孔子6.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 孔子6.html]]></title>
        <content><![CDATA[过而不改，是谓过矣。 Not to mend the fault one has made is to err indeed. 言必信，行必果。 Keep what you say and carry out what you do. 逝者如斯夫，不舍昼夜。 It passes on just like this, not ceasing day or night! 人无远虑，必有近忧。 If a man takes no thought about what is distant, he will find sorrow near at hand. ]]></content>
    </entry>
</search>
