<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<search chunksize="5">
    <entry index="1">
        <url><![CDATA[note.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[My Note]]></title>
        <keywords><![CDATA[[file, 博士后, 博士, 留下, refs, privoxy, conversion, nested, 可能, template, boolean, 确实, 使用, const, isalpha, make, directory, defined, 非常, allow, think, 人数, avoid, safe, approach, tolower, technique, confdir, 收录, 撒网, 学校, fulltext, obvious, 现在, 教师, note, 国内, 高校, error, 应当, created, support, good, wrote, test, vs, goal, odd, 偶数, validity]]]></keywords>
        <summary><![CDATA[[please put the required file(s)in the (confdir)/templates directory. The location of the (confdir) directory is specified in the main Privoxy config file. (It’s typically the Privoxy install directory). 100 101 102 ambiguity, isalpha defined in or (). tolower, refs and see also tolower, Learn how to validate objects in a boolean context without the usual harmful side effects. The Goal Test their validity in Boolean contexts The Obvious Approach Is, If you think that this situation can be saved with a little const trickery]]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry index="2">
        <url><![CDATA[README.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[Wikify - Build wiki from my notes]]></title>
        <keywords><![CDATA[[file, jar, 搜索, 生成, 举例, 数据, 使用, build, notes, 用于, run, wiki, 页面, 参考, wikify, wikify, pandoc, java]]]></keywords>
        <summary><![CDATA[[Wikify - Build wiki from my notes build jar file, 用于页面搜索, 参考]]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry index="3">
        <url><![CDATA[图灵的光环.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[图灵的光环]]></title>
        <keywords><![CDATA[[图灵, 设计, 图灵机, 机器, 理论, 其实, 计算, 计算机, 演算, church, lambda, ace, 论文, 东西, 后来, enigma, 叫做, utm, 作者, 最后, 发明, 现在, npl, 实际, 发表, 工程师, turing, 已经, edvac, 知道, 问题, 简单, 工作, 模型, 更加, 觉得, 贡献, 启发, 发现, 破解, 使用, 基本, 研究, 解释, 理解, 能够, 电子计算机, bombe, 复杂, 几乎]]]></keywords>
        <summary><![CDATA[[图灵设计了这机器, 图灵的理论不但没能启发任何计算机的设计, P 图灵设计的唯一一个计算机ACE, 所以图灵的理论启发了所有这些机器, 他把图灵的机器叫做]]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry index="4">
        <url><![CDATA[如果让我重做一次研究生.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 如果让我重做一次研究生.html]]></title>
        <keywords><![CDATA[[论文, 东西, 重要, 学习, 知识, 老师, 研究生, 学生, 问题, 领域, 里面, 非常, 知道, 大学, 应该, 题目, 时间, 可能, 思考, 一定, 博士, 英文, 训练, 好好, 慢慢, 文章, 念书, 生活, 教授, 完成, 不要, 阶段, 学术, 清楚, 办法, 必须, 常常, 硕士, 发现, 研究, 相关, 认为, 时代, 太多, 最重要, 创新, 已经, 觉得, 成为, 后来]]]></keywords>
        <summary><![CDATA[[同时也知道碰到问题可以看哪些东西, 我的学生常常选非常难的题目, 二、一个老师怎么训练研究生 身为老师你要怎么训练研究生, （三）论文的正式写作 1. 学习有所取舍 到了写论文的时候, 常常一篇硕士论文或博士论文最重要、最关键的]]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry index="5">
        <url><![CDATA[孔子1.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 孔子1.html]]></title>
        <keywords><![CDATA[[learn, knowledge, continually, acquiring, new, learning, teacher, nature, fond, 时习之, active, pleasant, 不耻下问, constant, 敏而好, application, perseverance, old, ashamed, cherishing, ask, keeps, man, inferiors]]]></keywords>
        <summary><![CDATA[[and he was not ashamed to ask and learn of his inferiors., He was of an active nature and yet fond of learning]]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry index="6">
        <url><![CDATA[孔子2.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 孔子2.html]]></title>
        <keywords><![CDATA[[qualities, teachers, delightful, select, 不亦乐乎, 远方, want, 勿施于人, 己所不欲, serve, friends, good, follow, bad, avoid, walk, coming, 不善, distant, 三人行, quarters]]]></keywords>
        <summary><![CDATA[[they may serve me as my teachers. I will select their good qualities and follow them, their bad qualities and avoid them. 己所不欲, Is it not delightful to have friends coming from distant quarters]]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry index="7">
        <url><![CDATA[孔子3.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 孔子3.html]]></title>
        <keywords><![CDATA[[feels, lose, discomposure, familiar, behave, men, note, difficult, servants, 不同, 相为谋, girls, people, courses, different, 为难, lay, 小人, plans, 女子, humility, virtue, maintain, complete, reserve, man, discontented, 君子]]]></keywords>
        <summary><![CDATA[[they lose their humility. If you maintain a reserve towards them, they are discontented.]]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry index="8">
        <url><![CDATA[孔子4.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 孔子4.html]]></title>
        <keywords><![CDATA[[heart, longer, right, 逾矩, set, boundaries, overstepped, afflicted, learning, thirty, desired, planted, heaven, docile, heard, biddings, firm, seventy, ear, ground, feet, dictates, knew, fifty, perplexities, suffered, follow, 不知, 从心所欲, men, 耳顺, knowing, 知天命, 不惑, know]]]></keywords>
        <summary><![CDATA[[At fifteen I set my heart upon learning. At thirty, I no longer suffered from perplexities. At fifty, I knew what were the biddings of Heaven. At sixty, I will be afflicted that I do not know men., I heard them with docile ear. At seventy]]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry index="9">
        <url><![CDATA[孔子5.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 孔子5.html]]></title>
        <keywords><![CDATA[[man, men, wishes, 君子, superior, qualities, perfect, nearly, work, nature, 习相远, sharpen, 相近, opposite, mean, alike, tools, 敏于行, seeks, conduct, earnest, 成人之, 小人, slow, 成人之美, speech, bad, practice, admirable, craftsman, seek, wide, 必先利其器, apart, 工欲善其事]]]></keywords>
        <summary><![CDATA[[The superior man seeks to perfect the admirable qualities of men, The superior man wishes to be slow in his speech and earnest in his conduct. 君子成人之美, and does not seek to perfect their bad qualities.The mean man does the opposite of this. 性相近也, A craftsman who wishes to do his work well must first sharpen his tools. 君子欲讷于言, men are nearly alike]]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry index="10">
        <url><![CDATA[孔子6.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[(No Title) 孔子6.html]]></title>
        <keywords><![CDATA[[行必果, takes, say, man, 远虑, carry, 逝者, night, day, 不舍, 昼夜, ceasing, passes, 言必信, thought, err, distant, sorrow, fault, mend, hand]]]></keywords>
        <summary><![CDATA[[he will find sorrow near at hand.]]]></summary>
    </entry>
    <entry index="11">
        <url><![CDATA[生活方式.html]]></url>
        <title><![CDATA[生活方式]]></title>
        <keywords><![CDATA[[东西, 街头, 地方, 方式, 感到, 已经, 上海, 毫无, 喜欢, 觉得, 品牌, 女人, 排队, 作者, 商场, 流行, 城市, 商品化, 一起, 积分, 很难, 餐厅, 也许, 世界, 完全, 兴趣, 打车, 越来越, 走路, 门口, 购物, 文艺, 有兴趣, 等候, 真的, 厌烦, 股市, 店铺, 电影, 签约, 简书, 股票, 生活, 小区, 姿势, ed, com, dd, ab, jianshu]]]></keywords>
        <summary><![CDATA[[积分多少可以换某些东西, 对街头女人的某种走路姿势也越来越看不惯, 还有些玩积分的地方, 或者男人的生活方式已经比女人还精致了, 我曾试图在上海街头找一些机械加工的地方]]]></summary>
    </entry>
</search>
